[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community
Okay. Well, we've talked quite extensively about
好的 我们已经十分深入地探讨了关于
using regression for the task of predicting house value, but of course,
使用回归模型来解决预测房屋价格的问题 但是当然
the number of applications in which regression can be used are quite large.
那些可以运用回归模型的应用问题的数量 是十分巨大的
Let's discuss just a few examples.
让我们来讨论其中的一些例子
So one is for
其中一个是
predicting your salary after you take this Machine Learning specialization.
预测你在学习了这一系列的机器学习专业课程后 所能得到的薪资
So you work really, really hard in this specialization, and
所以当你非常非常地努力学习这一系列专业课程后
hopefully after that, you can go earn a really cool job, have a very big salary.
但愿在这之后 你能够获得一份很酷的工作 挣很高的薪资
But to predict how much your salary will be, maybe that depends on things like,
但是要预测你的薪资可能会是多少 可能这就依赖于一些事物 比如
what was your performance in the various courses of the specialization?
你在这系列专业课程的不同课程中的表现如何？
What was the quality of your capstone project?
你毕业项目的质量如何？
How many forum responses did you make?
你在论坛上回复了多少帖子？
And so on.
类似种种
Okay. When we think about predicting your
好的 当我们考虑去预测你的
salary, y hat What we're gonna do is we're gonna estimate our model parameters, w0,
薪资 y hat 的时候 我们所要做的 就是估计我们的模型的参数 w0
w1, w2 and w3, which are our intercept and our weights on your performance in
w1 w2和w3 这些是我们模型的截距大小 以及一系列的权值 对应于你课堂的表现
the class, the quality of your capstone, and your participation in the forum.
你的毕业项目的质量 和你在讨论区的参与程度
And when we're estimating these model parameters, what we're gonna use,
我们会估计这些模型的参数 我们将会使用到这些
we're gonna use these features for other students who have taken this course and
我们将会把这些特征应用在其他选修这门课的学生身上
the observations of what their salaries were and
以及我们观测到的 他们的薪资到底是多少
the jobs they got after taking this Machine Learning Specialization.
以及他们在选修这门机器学习专业课程之后 所获得的工作
Another application of regression is for doing stock prediction.
另一个回归分析的应用就是股市的预测
So here, we might think about the fact that the prediction for
在这里 我们会考虑这样的一个事实 那就是
the price of a stock tomorrow depends on the recent history of the stock price.
对明天股市价格的预测 是依赖于最近股市价格的历史数据的
It depends on news events, different things going on in the world,
这依赖于一些新闻事件 即在世界上发生的各种不同的事
as well as the value of other related commodities.
以及那些相关的商品的价值
And a very different application than thinking about predicting stock prices or
回归分析还有一种非常特殊的应用 比之于预测股市的价格
your salary after this specialization is you're sitting on Twitter,
以及预测你在选修这门专业课程之后的薪资十分不同 那就是推特的转发 想象你正在使用推特
you tweet something, and
你正在发一条推特的时候
you wanna know how many people are gonna eventually retweet what you just tweeted.
你想要知道最终会有多少的用户 转发你刚刚发送的那条推特
Well, this might depend on how many followers you have, how many followers
这就依赖于你有多少关注者
your followers have, different features of the text of what you tweeted,
你的关注者们有多少关注者 你发送的推特文本中的不同特征
the popularity of the hashtag you included,
以及你的推特所包含的标签的受欢迎程度
number of past retweets of your tweets that you've had, and things like this.
以及你过去的推特有多少转发量 等等诸如此类的特征
And it turns out these types of models can actually be really good at predicting
结果表明这一类的模型事实上十分擅长于预测
the eventual number of retweets of your tweet.
你的推特的最终转发次数
And another very different application is maybe you have a smart house,
另一个与众不同的应用可能在于智能居室 想象一下你有一套智能的居室
there's lots of different sensors in this house, and
在这个居室中有许多不同的传感器
lots of different things you can control like temperature settings in different
并且有许多不同的事情是你可以控制的 比如不同的位置温度的设置
locations, vents, window blinds, and things like this.
比如通风口 百叶窗以及诸如此类的等等
And you have a home office and you have a desk, and you wanna be able to predict
然后你有一间家庭办公室和一张办公桌 并且你希望有能力去预测
what's the temperature at your desk based on various settings of all these controls.
你的办公桌的温度 基于所有这些控制器的种种不同的设置
But there's actually no sensor directly at your desk.
但是实际上在你的办公桌上没有直接的传感器
So, what you can think about doing is
所以你能够考虑去做的是
fitting a spatial model in order to predict what the temperature is
拟合一个空间的模型来预测
at all these different locations throughout the house.
整个居室中所有不同位置的温度
And this might depend on features such as the thermostat settings in the house,
这个预测可能会依赖于一些特征 比如居室中温度调节器的设定
whether the blinds are open or closed, temperature outside, how you've
百叶窗是打开的还是关闭的 居室外的温度 你是如何
set different vents, and as well as things like the time of the day, okay?
设置不同的通风口 以及像是一天中的时间这样的特征 对吗？
So, hopefully, you see that applications of regression, and
好的 但愿你已经了解了回归分析的应用
this really just touches the tip of the iceberg of where regression is used, but
实际上这仅仅触及了应用了回归分析的问题的冰山一角
it's really quite a powerful tool.
但它确实是一个强有力的工具
[MUSIC]
[背景音乐] 翻译: RyukaSuu |审阅: 19waa Coursera Global Translator Community